quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "Chandler’s organization needs to use a non-IP protocol on their VPN. Which of the common VPN protocols should he select to natively handle non-IP protocols?",
        "correct_answer": "L2TP",
        "options": ["PPTP", "L2F", "L2TP", "IPSec"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hosts are available on the subnet mask 255.255.255.224?",
        "correct_answer": "30",
        "options": ["28", "30", "29", "31"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The best describes the Bell-LaPadula Model.",
        "correct_answer": "No read-up, no write-down",
        "options": ["No write-up, no read-down", "No read-up, no write-down", "No read-up, no write-up", "No read-down, no write-down"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a preventative control?",
        "correct_answer": "IPS",
        "options": ["IPS", "IDS", "OS Upgrade", "Hot Site"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a preventative control?",
        "correct_answer": "Security Awareness Training",
        "options": ["Security Awareness Training", "Vulnerability Mitigation", "System monitoring", "Server Isolation"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does VNC operate across?",
        "correct_answer": "5900",
        "options": ["5800", "5600", "5900", "5700"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a corrective security control?",
        "correct_answer": "Backup Data Restore",
        "options": ["IDS", "Firewall", "Backup Data Restore", "Anti-Malware"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mitigation security controls should be implemented based on which of the following strategies?",
        "correct_answer": "Prevention",
        "options": ["Prevention", "Detection", "Reaction", "Recovery"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Technological vulnerabilities include which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": "Processes",
        "options": ["Processes", "Configuration", "Design", "Implementation"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What UDP port is typically used by the syslog service?",
        "correct_answer": "514",
        "options": ["514", "515", "443", "445"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What service uses the port 993?",
        "correct_answer": "Secure IMAP",
        "options": ["POP", "Secure POP", "Secure IMAP", "Secure SMTP"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many subnets on the following subnet mask 255.128.0.0?",
        "correct_answer": "2",
        "options": ["16", "2", "4", "8"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which symmetric block cipher algorithm just applies a key to the block?",
        "correct_answer": "Electronic Code Book",
        "options": ["Cipher Feedback", "Output Feedback", "Electronic Code Book", "Cipher Block Chaining"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Colleen is conducting a business impact assessment for her organization. What metric provides important information about the amount of time that the organization may be without a service before causing irreparable harm?",
        "correct_answer": "MTD",
        "options": ["RTO", "ALE", "RPO", "MTD"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following can vulnerabilities be valued on?",
        "correct_answer": "Ease of exploitation.",
        "options": ["Ease of exploitation.", "Weakness of the security properties.", "Number of attempts.", "Threats."]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the books in the Rainbow Series deals with password management?",
        "correct_answer": "Green Book",
        "options": ["Green Book", "Tan Book", "Blue Book", "Orange Book"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Monica has discovered that the smart card-based locks used to keep the facility she works at secure are not effective because staff members are propping the doors open. She places signs on the doors reminding staff that leaving the door open creates a security issue, and she adds alarms that will sound if the doors are left open for more than five minutes. What type of controls has she put into place?",
        "correct_answer": "Compensating",
        "options": ["Physical", "Recovery", "Compensating", "Administrative"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Michelle is in charge of her organization’s mobile device management efforts and handles lost and stolen devices. Which of the following recommendations will provide the most assurance to her organization that data will not be lost if a device is stolen?",
        "correct_answer": "Full device encryption and mandatory passcodes",
        "options": ["Mandatory passcodes and application management", "Enabling GPS tracking and full device encryption", "Full device encryption and mandatory passcodes", "Remote wipe and GPS tracking"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The web application that Ross’s development team is working on needs to provide secure session management that can prevent hijacking of sessions using the cookies that the application relies on. Which of the following techniques would be the best for him to recommend to prevent this?",
        "correct_answer": "Set the Secure attribute for the cookies, thus forcing TLS",
        "options": ["Set the Secure attribute for the cookies, thus forcing TLS", "Set the HTTPOnly attribute to require only unencrypted sessions", "Set the Domain cookie attribute to example.com to limit cookie access to servers in the same domain.", "Set the Expires cookie attribute to less than a week"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port number does MSSQL listen for connections?",
        "correct_answer": "1433",
        "options": ["53", "1433", "3389", "443"]
    }
]